{
    "id": "0d7d189684f64f60a5eaf711a988f997",
    "title": "Or, Or Else, Otherwise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f92c3ea785de4d99bff23fa27c12ae7f",
            "title": "Or, Or Else, Otherwise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We must hurry up .................... we will be late for the party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or",
                        "otherwise",
                        "but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I must reach home before 8 oâ€™clock ............................. my mother will get angry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "otherwise",
                        "or"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You must work hard ....................... you will fail.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or",
                        "otherwise",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ought to put the meat in the oven now, ............................ dinner will not be ready when the guests arrive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or",
                        "or else",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Walk carefully .................... you will fall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or else",
                        "unless",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Leave at once .......................... I will call the police.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or else",
                        "unless",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Consult a doctor immediately, ....................... your health will get worse.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or else",
                        "unless",
                        "otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We must water the plants ........................., they will die.",
                    "description": "Otherwise is not a conjunction. It is a transitive adverb. We use a semicolon before otherwise. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "otherwise",
                        "or"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Put the milk in the fridge ....................... it will turn sour.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or",
                        "otherwise",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He should start exercising ............................, he will get fat.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or",
                        "otherwise",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}